[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
[Abyss]
Who let you in?
Fan Jie.
I know why you're here.
But I'm a police officer.
We need evidence to handle a case.
Right now, all evidence points to
your mom dying in a traffic accident.
Impossible.
How could it be such a coincidence?
The one who ran over my mom
happens to be that bitch's colleague.
How is that possible?
I understand how you feel.
But just because the driver knows Du Juan
doesn't mean she ordered it.
We can't solve cases on speculation alone.
If your investigation was solid enough,
would I need to speculate? Would I?
We're not just investigating
for you alone!
I've told you already.
The driver was drunk.
The speed, route, and angle of impact
all match an accident.
He has also pleaded guilty
and accepted the punishment.
The case is legally closed.
Officer Xin, I'm begging you.
Please investigate it again.
Please.
She's my mom.
She was holding
the scrambled eggs she made for me.
People saw it.
They said when she was hit,
the box was crushed.
Her brains, her blood, and the eggs
were all mixed together.
You couldn't even tell them apart.
I beg you to look into it again.
What did my mom do wrong?
Did she deserve to be run over
because she didn't make way
for that bitch sooner?
I'm begging you.
Officer Xin, please investigate it again.
-Please investigate it again.
-Kid.
Kneeling only gets you sympathy,
not the truth.
I'm a police officer.
I only care about right and wrong,
not personal feelings.
Captain Xin, we got news.
The target has appeared.
Let's go.
Come on, get up, get up.
You can't just walk in here.
This is an office.
It holds classified information.
Come on.
Mom.
Today is the 49th day since you passed.
I'm here to see you.
I found a job.
Working at the internet cafe
near our home.
The boss is pretty nice,
and the work isn't tiring.
I can
support myself now.
The police have their rules,
and a son has his duty.
I will settle the score
with those who hurt you,
one by one.
Take care
♪ I once fell into a dream ♪
on your way.
Just wait and see.
No!
♪ Inside I lost my name ♪
♪ The sun hit my face straight ♪
♪ And left me ashamed. Who is who? ♪
Dad.
The doctor said
the tumor on your liver
is bigger than a fist.
There's nothing they can do.
♪ Who is who? ♪
♪ Who bears deep sin still praying? ♪
Mom is over there
♪ Who is who? ♪
♪ Who shuts their eyes
and begs for rights? ♪
waiting for you so long.
♪ Why is the blade red with the blood? ♪
You've lived on borrowed time for years.
♪ They call it just and true ♪
♪ Why is the slaughter made so cold? ♪
It's time to go to the underworld
and make amends to her.
♪ They say it was meant to ♪
♪ Why can the one who saves not save? ♪
♪ Why does the one
who fights to guard me? ♪
♪ Why did they chain your two hands? ♪
♪ Then judge what they believe? ♪
♪ All things will fade into night ♪
♪ Your mind will break, then take flight ♪
[Episode 14]
Bro.
[Ping'an Urban District]
Wake up, bro.
I'm turning right at the intersection
ahead to deliver goods.
After unloading, I'll get on the highway.
I'm not going into the city.
You can get off here.
Thanks.
See you.
[Ping'an Urban District]
One, come on, go.
Mr. Li!
Come down for a sec.
What's wrong?
Mr. Li, look.
These marks
look like an impact crater
formed by someone
jumping from a high place
and landing on their forefeet.
Right.
They even tried to fill it with dirt
to cover their tracks.
But they left in a hurry
and didn't clean it up properly.
I'll contact the forensics team right away
to see if they can extract
the footprints and fingerprints.
Okay.
Zhang Alin.
From 2002 to 2006,
did you work
at Zhang Quan's construction site
and share a dorm with Song Laifu?
Yes, Officer.
How was your relationship?
Reporting. It was okay.
Take a close look at this person.
You don't have to answer me right away.
Think carefully.
He looks a bit like Song Laifu,
quite tall.
He wasn't at the site for long
and disappeared
around the same time as Song Laifu.
Reporting.
I-I have some impression of him.
Tell me about it.
He was only there for a few months.
This guy didn't talk much
and didn't like interacting with people.
But he was pretty ruthless.
With one swing of a hammer,
he nailed someone's hand to the bed board.
Newbie?
Got any smokes?
Yeah,
under the mattress. Get them yourself.
Where?
Next time you do this,
I'll nail your neck.
Well, we didn't live together.
I didn't dare to tell
anyone about this.
I was afraid he'd get back at me.
Do you know his name?
Back then, Song Laifu and I
both called him San.
Because he was the third child
in his family.
His surname seemed to be Guo.
Guo San...
Guo San something...
Reporting. I can't remember.
Do you know anything else?
Right.
Song Laifu
seemed to have asked him
where he was from.
He said his hometown was Quanlin County.
[Dedicated to Duty,
Build a Harmonious Prison Compound]
Hurry up and go to Quanlin County.
Call Xu Ling and ask her to issue
another investigation notice for us.
Okay.
Let's go.
[Dedicated to Duty,
Build a Harmonious Prison Compound]
Captain Fan.
How is it?
The murder weapon is confirmed.
It's the bronze antelope ornament
from Han Pinmu's home.
Although it was wiped,
a trace amount of blood
was still extracted
from the gap at the bottom.
DNA matching
has confirmed it belongs to Han Pinmu.
What about the fingerprints?
The fingerprints on the outer edge
of the window matched
Chen Chunli's.
So suspicion against Xin
should be lessened.
Why would Chen Chunli
go to Han Pinmu's home?
Although a complete shoe print
couldn't be extracted
from the impact crater outside the window,
judging by the size and depth,
it was a female
weighing about 50 kilograms.
Combined with Chen Chunli's fingerprints
we extracted from the outer edge
of the window,
[Huangshui Public Security Bureau]
[Fingerprint Identification Report]
we can almost determine that
on the night of the incident,
besides Xin Jiran and Han Pinmu,
Chen Chunli also accessed the crime scene.
Li Cheng,
you just said the murder weapon was wiped.
Yes.
Not only was the murder weapon wiped,
but also the floor
and the inside of the window.
If Chen Chunli had been in such a hurry
that she had to jump out of
the second-floor window to escape,
she wouldn't have had time
to clean up the scene.
Could it be that
someone was cleaning up after her?
Very likely.
Chen Chunli entered Han Pinmu's home
before Xin Jiran went there.
This is really strange.
Han Pinmu is a family member
of the victim
in the 4th case of the 3/12 Case.
Chen Chunli
is the direct victim of the 5th case.
Why would they meet
at Han Pinmu's home?
Stop guessing.
Summon Chen Chunli immediately.
Chunli, you're here.
What are you buying today?
I sprained my ankle while working.
I'm here to buy some medicine.
Why are you always so careless?
Alright, use this then.
Take this one.
It's a big brand,
and most importantly, it's very cheap.
Just rub some on when you get home,
and you'll be fine.
It works wonders.
Here, take a bag.
No need.
Look at you,
working so hard
at your age.
-In my opinion—
-How much is it?
I'll give you a discount.
Just 15.
Like I was saying,
you need someone who cares for you, right?
As the old saying goes,
everyone needs a companion in old age.
It's just about having someone
to pour water
or buy medicine
when you're sick, right?
I'm used to living alone.
Thank you.
Take care then.
Chen Chunli.
We're from the county police.
[Police] [Xiao Jie]
Come with us.
Is there a problem?
You'll know when we get there.
[Police] [Li Cheng]
Name.
[Ping'an City Cultural Activity Center,
Ping'an Province]
Then I'll schedule you
for Friday evening from 7 to 8.
Is that okay?
Yes, thank you.
Hello.
S-Sir, hello.
Are you inquiring about classes
or signing up for a membership?
Looking for someone.
Looking for someone?
I'm really sorry, Sir.
We're already closed for the day.
And the staff have all left.
How about you come back tomorrow?
Officer,
the patient is awake and wants to see you.
The doctor will be here shortly.
Be careful.
The patient just regained consciousness
and shouldn't be agitated.
Why is it you?
Where is Li Cheng?
He's on a mission.
He's not here.
Get him here.
What do you want with Li Cheng?
I'm turning myself in.
Captain Fan.
Wait.
The patient just woke up. He needs rest.
Too many people.
I can't breathe.
Just leave Li Cheng here alone.
Speak.
What do you want to say?
Visiting a dying patient
without even bringing flowers or fruit?
You just came empty-handed?
You want to turn yourself in.
For which crime?
Du Juan.
I killed her.
With whom?
Hu Xiaofei and Xin Xiaoliang.
Xin Xiaoliang?
W-What about her?
Are you surprised?
After all these years,
you haven't found a single clue.
Do you still think she died innocent?
How did you kill her?
On the night of April 17, 2004,
we broke into Du Juan's dorm
and tied her up.
Originally, I just wanted to ask
if she was the one
who instigated Fang Meng
to hit my mom.
But this bitch
denied it
and dared to curse my mom.
Since she had a death wish,
I had to send her on her way.
What did you use to kill her?
Stabbed her to death
with a triangular scraper.
Where did it come from?
Xiaofei brought it.
Xiaofei had committed crimes
with Song Laifu
and Zhang Chengguo.
He knew their methods.
Who stabbed her?
Does it matter?
Who?
The three of us each stabbed her once.
A blood pact.
This is the first stab.
Two more to go.
You guys do it.
Your turn.
Did you want to kill her
from the very beginning?
I just wanted the truth.
She didn't know what was good for her,
so I made my move.
If you really are
one of the true culprits of the 3/12 Case,
tell us something we don't know.
We killed Du Juan by imitating
Song Laifu
and Zhang Chengguo's modus operandi,
wanting to frame them.
Later, I was worried
things would be exposed,
so I finally made up my mind
to get rid of Song Laifu.
Unfortunately, I was a step too late
and got Xiaofei killed.
It took some effort
when I killed Song Laifu.
I originally wanted to frame Xin Jiran,
but unfortunately, I failed.
You just said
that you and Xin Xiaoliang
had a relationship
in which you could kill together.
Then why did you frame
Xin Xiaoliang's father for the murder,
who was also a former police officer?
As a father,
he caused the death of his own son,
my good brother Xin Xiaoliang.
As a police officer,
he knew my mom's death was suspicious
but didn't investigate.
Do you think he deserves to be a father
or a police officer?
Is killing
the only way out for you?
[Ping'an City Cultural Activity Center,
Ping'an Province]
Go on.
What else?
Someone took Song Laifu's identity.
You already know that, right?
His real name is Guo Sanjun.
That's not enough.
I need direct evidence.
There's an encrypted hard drive
in the drawer at my internet cafe.
It has what you want.
A hard drive?
What's the password?
If you can't even guess that,
I'll be very disappointed, Officer Li.
Why turn yourself in all of a sudden?
As a friend,
I'm giving your career a boost.
And I hope that when I go to hell,
the King of Hell will give me some credit
for confessing.
We all agree that
Han Pinmu forged the group photo
to protect the third person
who hasn't been exposed.
But Xin Xiaoliang has long been dead.
Who is he putting on this show for
with all this effort?
Li Cheng.
Li Cheng!
Captain Fan.
How's it going with the password?
The cybersecurity colleagues
are working on it.
But they said
cracking a hard drive
with such strong encryption
would take at least a few days.
None of the passwords
I could think of worked.
Repeat
what he said
about Chen Chunli.
He said Chen Chunli
somehow found out that
the police suspected Han Pinmu
was the suspect in the 3/12 Case.
So Chen Chunli went to him for revenge.
But Han Pinmu told her
he only killed Du Juan
and wasn't involved in her case.
Chen Chunli didn't believe him
and hit him with something.
Not long after she hit him,
Xin Jiran knocked on the door.
She recognized Xin Jiran's voice
and jumped out the window,
afraid of being charged
by the police with assault.
If so,
why did he need to clean up the scene?
His surrender seems reasonable,
but it's actually full of
suspicious points.
You guys are the ones saying everything.
You said it yourselves
that this guy was suspicious,
tracking and tailing.
Now that he's surrendered,
you're hesitating
and acting all coy.
How long has it been?
You have to give me a result,
so I can report back.
What's the rush?
We've waited for 8 years.
A little longer won't hurt.
Right,
what about Guo Sanjun?
Still no news from Hu Sen.
If it's true,
he's deeply involved
with the suspect in the 3/12 Case.
Xu Ling,
make a call and ask. Be quick.
Okay.
Chen Chunli is still tight-lipped?
Yeah,
she's as hard as nails.
Then interrogate her again
based on the clues
provided by Han Pinmu.
Pry her mouth open
no matter what.
Don't move.
If you don't put medicine on this ankle,
you won't be able to walk.
I noticed you were limping
as soon as you walked in.
You can't hold on anymore
after sitting for so long, right?
You've been through a lot,
yet you climbed walls and jumped
off buildings like a youngster.
At your age,
your bones can't take a fall.
Han Pinmu has surrendered.
Look familiar?
I've seen it.
Eight years ago,
this photo was posted all over the city.
You were offering a reward for this man.
You have a good memory
and strong nerves.
What does this have to do with Han Pinmu
turning himself in?
The man in the photo is him?
What do you think he confessed to?
What else could it be?
He's a murderer
and a rapist.
You should have arrested
him a long time ago.
So you admit
that you attacked him
because you suspected
he was the one who hurt you back then?
I admit I hit Han Pinmu.
With what?
The bronze antelope ornament on his table.
He's a grown man.
He just stood there and let you hit him?
He didn't fight back?
He seemed very sick,
coughing non-stop.
So he wasn't even as strong as me.
Then why did you escape
through the window?
After I hit him,
his head kept bleeding,
which terrified me.
Then I heard someone banging on the door.
Judging by the voice,
it should be Xin Jiran.
Han Pinmu!
Open the door!
I know his relationship with the police.
If he saw
I beat someone up like that,
he would definitely arrest me.
So I pushed Han Pinmu away
and jumped out
the window
in his bedroom's bathroom.
What did Han Pinmu say
when you confronted him?
What else could he say?
Just making excuses.
People like him
are full of lies.
Back then, you clearly identified
the 3 people who hurt you
as 2 middle-aged men
and one young man.
Han Pinmu and Bi Dehua
are about the same age.
They are obviously not middle-aged.
So why did you think it was him?
I've said it many times.
It was too dark then,
and the scene was very chaotic.
I might have just identified
the wrong person.
Or I just saw it wrong, right?
You can't expect someone
who almost died
to clearly remember
every detail of the crime scene.
With your logic and reflexes,
being a cleaner is a waste of your talent.
I admit I hit Han Pinmu.
I'll accept
whatever sentence or punishment
you give me.
You can go.
Han Pinmu said
he wouldn't press charges against you.
Chen Chunli.
Do you hate him?
Yes.
More than that.
I wanted to kill him with my own hands.
That night 8 years ago,
he ruined my whole life.
He ruined my entire family too.
He deserves to die.
Even if he dies 100 times,
he can never atone for his sins.
What do you think?
The hatred is real.
Do you believe her?
It doesn't look like they colluded.
It's more like they know
each other so well
that knowing Han Pinmu turned himself in
gave her confidence.
The two of them cooperated
and put on a show.
At least, it proves
Xin had nothing to do
with Han Pinmu's injury.
[Ruijiexing Technology Co., Ltd.]
Whose phone ends in 6783?
Mine.
Here.
Someone just dropped it off.
Said to give it to the person
whose phone ends in 6783.
It's not a courier?
No,
a guy brought it.
He said that he was passing it on
for someone else,
and that it had to be delivered today.
Okay, got it. Thanks.
You're welcome.
[Technical Support & Training
Industrial Internet Industry]
Is Hao asleep?
Yes.
He cried for half an hour after feeding.
Finally got him to sleep.
Thanks for your hard work.
Pengfei.
I want to go back to work.
Okay.
I'll talk to my uncle
in the next couple of days
to see if he can come help.
Honey.
Happy birthday.
Thanks.
You should get some rest.
I'll work a bit longer.
I'll do the night feeding.
-I'm going to sleep.
-Go to sleep.
[Happy Birthday]
[This PC]
[USB Drive]
[Travel Star] [Data Lock] [Unlock]
[Happy Birthday]
[Unlock Passphrase] [Unlock]
[Quick Unlock Progress]
[Data Lock] [Unlock]
[Unlock]
["Abyss"]
[Abyss]
Nothing in this world
makes me feel the value of life
more than your friendship.
There's still hope for him
to wake up, right?
All I can say is that
things are looking up.